{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451525553","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451525553"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" a208eafe-f3fb-4a20-bc5f-11992eb72bc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-U-CH"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451531523","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451531523"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" a208eafe-f3fb-4a20-bc5f-11992eb72bc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-U-CH"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451534871","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451534871"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" a208eafe-f3fb-4a20-bc5f-11992eb72bc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-J-H"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451565341","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451565341"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" c33573a0-52ff-4ffa-8e9b-db9877b18d6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_D_Z"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451571945","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451571945"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" c33573a0-52ff-4ffa-8e9b-db9877b18d6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_S_H"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451579503","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451579503"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" c33573a0-52ff-4ffa-8e9b-db9877b18d6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_S_H"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451589887","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451589887"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" c33573a0-52ff-4ffa-8e9b-db9877b18d6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_S_H"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451596506","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451596506"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" c33573a0-52ff-4ffa-8e9b-db9877b18d6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_O_L"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451604083","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451604082"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" c33573a0-52ff-4ffa-8e9b-db9877b18d6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_O_L"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451614453","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451614453"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" c33573a0-52ff-4ffa-8e9b-db9877b18d6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_O_L"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451620661","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451620661"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" c33573a0-52ff-4ffa-8e9b-db9877b18d6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_J_L_CH"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451628125","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451628125"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" c33573a0-52ff-4ffa-8e9b-db9877b18d6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_J_L_CH"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451646545","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451646544"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" c33573a0-52ff-4ffa-8e9b-db9877b18d6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_J_L_CH"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451655769","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451655768"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" c33573a0-52ff-4ffa-8e9b-db9877b18d6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_J_L_CH"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451669150","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451669150"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na Jimbi na Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451669736","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451669735"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na Jimbi na Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451669961","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451669961"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na Jimbi na Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451670465","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451670464"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na Jimbi na Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451671742","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451671741"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na Jimbi na Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451671993","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451671992"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na Jimbi na Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451672599","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451672598"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na Jimbi na Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIMBI"," userResponse":" JIMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451672925","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451672925"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na Jimbi na Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451673589","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451673589"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na Jimbi na Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451676389","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451676387"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa marafiki wakubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451677313","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451677313"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa marafiki wakubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451678198","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451678197"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa marafiki wakubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKUBWA"," userResponse":" WAKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451681344","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451681344"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja Sungura alimtembelea Jimbi na familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451682116","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451682115"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja Sungura alimtembelea Jimbi na familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451683254","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451683253"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja Sungura alimtembelea Jimbi na familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451684573","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451684573"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja Sungura alimtembelea Jimbi na familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMTEMBELEA"," userResponse":" ALIMTEMBELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451685137","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451685137"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja Sungura alimtembelea Jimbi na familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIMBI"," userResponse":" JIMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451685805","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451685804"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja Sungura alimtembelea Jimbi na familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451686739","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451686739"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja Sungura alimtembelea Jimbi na familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451687063","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451687062"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja Sungura alimtembelea Jimbi na familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451690340","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451690340"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifurahia chakula cha jioni pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFURAHIA"," userResponse":" WALIFURAHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451691112","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451691112"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifurahia chakula cha jioni pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451691351","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451691351"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifurahia chakula cha jioni pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451692011","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451692011"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifurahia chakula cha jioni pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451692806","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451692806"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifurahia chakula cha jioni pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451695925","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451695924"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa kwenda kulala ulifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451696121","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451696120"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa kwenda kulala ulifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451696584","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451696584"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa kwenda kulala ulifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451697360","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451697359"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa kwenda kulala ulifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451698585","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451698584"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa kwenda kulala ulifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIFIKA"," userResponse":" ULIFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451701375","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451701374"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walipolala vichwa vyao vilifichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451702332","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451702332"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walipolala vichwa vyao vilifichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451702957","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451702955"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walipolala vichwa vyao vilifichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451703944","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451703944"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walipolala vichwa vyao vilifichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIMBI"," userResponse":" JIMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451704696","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451704696"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walipolala vichwa vyao vilifichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451705607","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451705607"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walipolala vichwa vyao vilifichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451705858","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451705858"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walipolala vichwa vyao vilifichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451706952","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451706952"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walipolala vichwa vyao vilifichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOLALA"," userResponse":" WALIPOLALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451708051","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451708050"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walipolala vichwa vyao vilifichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VICHWA"," userResponse":" VICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451708726","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451708726"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walipolala vichwa vyao vilifichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAO"," userResponse":" VYAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451710200","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451710200"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walipolala vichwa vyao vilifichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIFICHWA"," userResponse":" VILIFICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451713292","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451713290"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walilala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451714155","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451714154"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walilala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451714726","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451714725"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walilala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451715424","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451715423"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walilala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIMBI"," userResponse":" JIMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451716000","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451715999"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walilala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451716650","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451716650"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walilala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451717244","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451717244"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walilala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451718512","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451718512"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walilala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALILALA"," userResponse":" WALILALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451719900","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451719900"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walilala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FOFOFO"," userResponse":" FOFOFO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451722346","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451722345"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yeye hakuweza kulala usiku kucha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451723356","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451723355"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yeye hakuweza kulala usiku kucha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451724172","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451724171"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yeye hakuweza kulala usiku kucha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451724945","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451724945"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yeye hakuweza kulala usiku kucha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451725517","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451725517"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yeye hakuweza kulala usiku kucha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHA"," userResponse":" KUCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451729037","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451729036"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi Sungura alitaka kujua siri ya Jimbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451729710","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451729709"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi Sungura alitaka kujua siri ya Jimbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451730571","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451730571"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi Sungura alitaka kujua siri ya Jimbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAKA"," userResponse":" ALITAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451731245","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451731245"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi Sungura alitaka kujua siri ya Jimbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJUA"," userResponse":" KUJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451731923","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451731923"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi Sungura alitaka kujua siri ya Jimbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIRI"," userResponse":" SIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451732018","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451732017"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi Sungura alitaka kujua siri ya Jimbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451732609","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451732608"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi Sungura alitaka kujua siri ya Jimbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIMBI"," userResponse":" JIMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451735164","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451735164"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninyi huweka wapi vichwa vyenu usiku?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINYI"," userResponse":" NINYI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451735883","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451735883"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninyi huweka wapi vichwa vyenu usiku?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUWEKA"," userResponse":" HUWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451736400","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451736400"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninyi huweka wapi vichwa vyenu usiku?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451736868","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451736867"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninyi huweka wapi vichwa vyenu usiku?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VICHWA"," userResponse":" VICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451737447","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451737447"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninyi huweka wapi vichwa vyenu usiku?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYENU"," userResponse":" VYENU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451738442","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451738442"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninyi huweka wapi vichwa vyenu usiku?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451741320","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451741319"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jimbi aliamua kumchezea shere Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIMBI"," userResponse":" JIMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451742901","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451742901"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jimbi aliamua kumchezea shere Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMUA"," userResponse":" ALIAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451744001","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451744000"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jimbi aliamua kumchezea shere Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMCHEZEA"," userResponse":" KUMCHEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451744616","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451744616"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jimbi aliamua kumchezea shere Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHERE"," userResponse":" SHERE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451745510","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451745509"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jimbi aliamua kumchezea shere Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451748284","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451748284"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451749336","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451749335"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451749804","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451749804"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451750846","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451750846"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451751520","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451751520"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451752519","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451752519"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNA"," userResponse":" TUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451753106","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451753105"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIRI"," userResponse":" SIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451753191","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451753191"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451753926","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451753925"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451756407","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451756407"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451756601","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451756601"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451757364","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451757363"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451758434","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451758434"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451759242","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451759242"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKATA"," userResponse":" HUKATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451759691","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451759691"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VICHWA"," userResponse":" VICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451760106","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451760106"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYETU"," userResponse":" VYETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451762359","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451762358"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451763039","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451763039"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VICHWA"," userResponse":" VICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451763936","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451763935"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451764634","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451764633"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HULALA"," userResponse":" HULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451765671","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451765671"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYEMA"," userResponse":" VYEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451766439","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451766438"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABISA"," userResponse":" KABISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451769338","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451769338"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha asubuhi sisi huvirejesha vichwa vyetu mwilini Jimbi alieleza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451770499","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451770498"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha asubuhi sisi huvirejesha vichwa vyetu mwilini Jimbi alieleza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451771293","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451771293"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha asubuhi sisi huvirejesha vichwa vyetu mwilini Jimbi alieleza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451772446","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451772446"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha asubuhi sisi huvirejesha vichwa vyetu mwilini Jimbi alieleza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUVIREJESHA"," userResponse":" HUVIREJESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451773002","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451773001"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha asubuhi sisi huvirejesha vichwa vyetu mwilini Jimbi alieleza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VICHWA"," userResponse":" VICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451773600","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451773599"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha asubuhi sisi huvirejesha vichwa vyetu mwilini Jimbi alieleza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYETU"," userResponse":" VYETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451774379","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451774378"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha asubuhi sisi huvirejesha vichwa vyetu mwilini Jimbi alieleza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWILINI"," userResponse":" MWILINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451775255","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451775255"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha asubuhi sisi huvirejesha vichwa vyetu mwilini Jimbi alieleza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIMBI"," userResponse":" JIMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451776425","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451776425"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha asubuhi sisi huvirejesha vichwa vyetu mwilini Jimbi alieleza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIELEZA"," userResponse":" ALIELEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451779819","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451779818"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikwenda nyumbani na kuiambia familia yake siri ya kuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451780834","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451780833"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikwenda nyumbani na kuiambia familia yake siri ya kuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" ALIKWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451781817","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451781816"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikwenda nyumbani na kuiambia familia yake siri ya kuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451782397","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451782396"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikwenda nyumbani na kuiambia familia yake siri ya kuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451783677","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451783677"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikwenda nyumbani na kuiambia familia yake siri ya kuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIAMBIA"," userResponse":" KUIAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451784659","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451784659"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikwenda nyumbani na kuiambia familia yake siri ya kuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451785002","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451785001"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikwenda nyumbani na kuiambia familia yake siri ya kuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451785970","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451785966"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikwenda nyumbani na kuiambia familia yake siri ya kuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIRI"," userResponse":" SIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451786122","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451786122"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikwenda nyumbani na kuiambia familia yake siri ya kuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451786756","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451786755"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikwenda nyumbani na kuiambia familia yake siri ya kuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451789464","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451789463"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Sungura iliamua kujaribu wao wenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451789726","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451789726"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Sungura iliamua kujaribu wao wenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451790504","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451790503"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Sungura iliamua kujaribu wao wenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451791538","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451791537"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Sungura iliamua kujaribu wao wenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIAMUA"," userResponse":" ILIAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451793049","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451793049"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Sungura iliamua kujaribu wao wenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJARIBU"," userResponse":" KUJARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451793385","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451793385"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Sungura iliamua kujaribu wao wenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451794198","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451794198"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Sungura iliamua kujaribu wao wenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYEWE"," userResponse":" WENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451797071","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451797070"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unafikiri nini kilichotokea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAFIKIRI"," userResponse":" UNAFIKIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451797523","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451797522"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unafikiri nini kilichotokea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451799088","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451799088"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unafikiri nini kilichotokea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOTOKEA"," userResponse":" KILICHOTOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451801843","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451801841"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Unafikiri nini kilichotokea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451801969","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451801969"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 6d8a17b5-6941-41a2-a4e9-16e5a7dc85f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unafikiri nini kilichotokea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOTOKEA"," userResponse":" KILICHOTOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451828786","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451828786"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451829822","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451829822"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451834755","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451834755"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451835807","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451835807"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451838649","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451838649"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451839685","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451839685"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451843057","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451843057"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451844109","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451844109"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451846904","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451846904"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451847935","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451847935"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451852423","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451852423"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451853477","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451853476"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451858655","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451858655"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451859690","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451859689"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451864420","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451864420"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451865469","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451865469"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451880488","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451880487"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" START_I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451882337","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451882337"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451883395","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451883395"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451886695","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451886694"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451887730","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451887730"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451890874","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451890873"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451891146","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451891146"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451891949","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451891949"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451894957","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451894957"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451899389","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451899389"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451900422","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451900422"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451904169","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451904169"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451905199","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451905199"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451909030","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451909030"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451910077","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451910077"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451919551","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451919550"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451920603","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451920603"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451924195","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451924195"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451925248","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451925248"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451931230","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451931230"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451932272","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451932271"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451938128","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451938128"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451939177","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451939177"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451948687","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451948687"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451949754","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451949754"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451952436","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451952436"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451952623","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451952623"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451953800","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451953799"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451956184","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451956184"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451960335","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451960335"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451961370","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451961370"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451964775","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451964775"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451964929","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451964929"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 5b1f5e5f-ea68-479a-b86f-1a5f1e6d6476"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451990771","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451990771"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 7eeff4f7-71b1-4a58-8f9a-e2bc6ebb6d42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_6-9-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452001023","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452001023"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 7eeff4f7-71b1-4a58-8f9a-e2bc6ebb6d42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_6-9-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452007945","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452007945"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 7eeff4f7-71b1-4a58-8f9a-e2bc6ebb6d42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_6-9-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452013685","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452013685"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 7eeff4f7-71b1-4a58-8f9a-e2bc6ebb6d42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-7-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452021797","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452021797"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 7eeff4f7-71b1-4a58-8f9a-e2bc6ebb6d42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-3-1"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452031319","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452031319"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 7eeff4f7-71b1-4a58-8f9a-e2bc6ebb6d42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-1-0"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452039477","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452039477"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 7eeff4f7-71b1-4a58-8f9a-e2bc6ebb6d42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-1-0"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452045824","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452045823"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 7eeff4f7-71b1-4a58-8f9a-e2bc6ebb6d42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_0-5-9"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452053934","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452053933"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 7eeff4f7-71b1-4a58-8f9a-e2bc6ebb6d42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-4-9"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452057931","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452057930"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 7eeff4f7-71b1-4a58-8f9a-e2bc6ebb6d42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-4-9"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452068409","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452068408"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 7eeff4f7-71b1-4a58-8f9a-e2bc6ebb6d42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-4-9"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452077808","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452077807"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 7eeff4f7-71b1-4a58-8f9a-e2bc6ebb6d42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-4-9"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452088124","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452088121"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 70af7efe-45a3-46a2-acbf-f9ead3710840"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" MAJI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452091365","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452091364"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 70af7efe-45a3-46a2-acbf-f9ead3710840"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" MAJI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452091552","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452091552"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_141149"," gameId":" 70af7efe-45a3-46a2-acbf-f9ead3710840"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" MAJI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}